To create a new DataFrame and fill it with our new PCA component data, I wrote this code.
为了创建新的 DataFrame 并填充新的 PCA 成分数据 我编写了这些代码
The first thing I'm doing is creating
首先创建一个全新的 DataFrame
a totally new DataFrame to hold all my new transformed data,
其中包含所有新转换的数据
and then I'm going to iterate through each data point in our PCA component data.
然后遍历 PCA 成分数据中的每个数据点
I'm getting our component values from what I saw before,
从之前看到的结果中获取成分值
getting the label, projection,
包括标签“projection”
and our float 32 tensor values.
以及float32_tensor.values
Then I'm passing this list of components,
然后传入这个成分列表
and appending it to our county's transformed DataFrame.
并将其附加到 counties_transformed DataFrame
Now, this is going to be all 33 of our PCA components for each of our data points.
这个是每个数据点的所有 33 个 PCA 成分
Next, I know I still want to index by state county just as in our county scale DataFrame.
接下来 像 counties_scaled DataFrame 一样 按照 State-County 设定索引
So I'm setting our index accordingly.
相应地设定索引
Then I know I only want to keep the top_n_components.
我知道我只想保留前 n 个成分
I don't want all 33 of these features,
不想保留所有 33 个特征
I want say the top seven,
例如保留前七位
and I know they're ordered from least to most important.
并且知道它们按照最不重要到最重要排序
So similar to how we've handled this before,
与之前的处理方式相似
I am getting a start index,
获取起始索引
and then I'm getting a selection of data from that start index onwards.
然后从该索引一直到最后 选定一些数据
Finally, I'll return that truncated DataFrame in reverse order.
然后反向返回截断的 DataFrame
So I'll have my top component as the first column in this transformed DataFrame.
最高的成分将是这个转换后 DataFrame 的第一列
Now, I can run this code and select top_n_components to create our new data,
现在运行代码并传入 n_top_components 的值来创建新数据
and I'll create our seven top components because I
我将创建前七位成分的数据
know that captures 80 percent of our data variance.
因为我知道前七位可以捕获 80% 的数据方差
So I'm calling my create transformed DataFrame function,
调用 create_transformed_df 函数
and passing in my PCA component data for each of my data points,
传入每个数据点的 PCA 成分数据
and the original county skilled DataFrame.
以及原始 counties_scaled DataFrame
Finally, I'm passing in seven top components.
最后将 n_top_components 设为 7
This is the resulting DataFrame.
这就是生成的 DataFrame
So I'm still indexing by state county,
依然按 State-County 设定索引
and they have the values for components one through components seven.
具有从 1-7 的成分值
I'll actually want to take one more step.
再执行一个步骤
Instead of having numerical values for each of these columns,
这些列名称是个数值
I'm going to create a list of columns that's more descriptive.
我将采用更加描述性的列名称
So component one, two, three,
例如 c_1 c_2 c_3 一直到 c_7
up to seven, then you can change these names to whatever you want.
你也可以设为其他名称
So now, I have a list of counties and their component values.
我获得了郡县列表及其成分值
Now that I have my transformed data,
转换数据后
I no longer need my PCA model endpoint.
我不再需要 PCA 模型端点
I can delete it with a call to our SageMaker session.delete_endpoint,
可以通过调用SageMaker session.delete_endpoint 删除端点
and passing in the name of our PCA predictor.
传入 PCA 预测器的名称
You should always make sure to delete your resources when you're no longer using them.
不使用资源后 一定要删除资源
Otherwise, you may incur extra processing or storage fees.
否则可能会产生额外的处理或存储费
Okay. So I want to recap all the steps that we've taken.
Ok下面总结下我们执行的步骤
We went from defining a PCA model,
我们先定义了 PCA 模型
to training it on some formatted data.
然后用格式化的数据训练模型
Then we took a look at the trained model attributes by
接着通过使用 mxnet 库加载模型文件
loading in the models at file with the MX net Library.
查看了训练过的模型的属性
We looked at the top_n components and how much variance they covered in our data,
我们查看了前 n 个成分解释的方差
and decided to use the top seven principal components in our final analysis.
并决定在最终分析时使用前七个主成分
We also care about the weights of the features that make up each component.
我们还查看了组成每个成分的特征权重
This allows us to better describe
这样可以更好地描述
the components that make up our transformed to training data.
组成转换后训练数据的成分
Then to finally create our transformed data,
最终为了创建转换后数据
we had to deploy our trained PCA model,
我们部署了训练过的 PCA 模型
and apply it to our Numpy training data,
并将其应用到 NumPy 训练数据上
and just now created a new transform to DataFrame.
我们创建了新的转换后 DataFrame
So this was a lot of demonstration around training and deploying a SageMaker model,
这些就是训练和部署 SageMaker 模型的过程 演示的内容比较多
and I left some of the data cleaning and transformation steps to you.
我把一些数据清理和转换步骤留给你来完成
Next, I want you to get practice with deploying models on your own.
接下来 请练习部署你自己的模型
So I'll give you some exercises around training and deploying a K-means clustering model.
我将布置一些关于训练和部署 K 均值聚类模型的练习
This final model will be created in a similar way to the PCA model.
最后这个模型的创建方式与 PCA 模型相似
You'll define a K-means estimator,
你需要定义 K 均值 estimator
passing in appropriate parameters and train it on this new transformed data.
传入相应的参数并用新转换的数据训练它
So read through the following exercises and instructions carefully,
请仔细阅读下面的练习和说明
and see if you can complete all of them.
看看是否能全部完成
Getting all the way to K-means model deployment
最终部署 K 均值模型
and even extracting the trained model attributes.
甚至提取出训练过的模型的属性
If you run into an error,
如果你遇到错误
try to debug as usual by looking through the logs and traces.
请通过日志和跟踪记录正常地调试
I'll provide instruction and an even linking to
我将提供一些说明
some relevant documentation which can help you
以及相关文档的链接
in passing in the correct arguments to a K-means model.
帮助你向 K 均值模型传入正确的参数
For example, the end goal will be to assign
最终目标是
clusters to each of our data points and say one,
向每个数据点分配聚类
which counties are assigned to each cluster?
并且问 第一 应该把每个郡县分配到哪个聚类？
Two, what that means as far as component and feature level makeup.
第二 这对于成分和特征级组成来说是什么意思？
This will allow us to describe
这些问题可以帮助我们描述
the demographics similarities and differences between counties generally.
郡县之间的一般相似性和差异